My name is Mr. Brown and this is
(由 TurboScribe.ai 转录。升级到无限制版以移除此消息。) 我是布朗老师，这是
a video for my second grade language class
为我二年级语言课录制的视频，
during the coronavirus quarantine in Comayagua, Honduras.
在洪都拉斯科马亚瓜的新冠病毒隔离期间。
Hello everybody, I hope all of you are
大家好，我希望你们所有人都
happy and that you are washing your hands.
开开心心，并且勤洗手。
Today our objective is to spell common verbs
今天我们的目标是拼写常见的动词，
and pronounce them correctly by watching a slideshow
并通过观看幻灯片正确地发音，
and writing the words together.
以及一起书写这些单词。
Does anybody know what a verb is?
有谁知道什么是动词吗？
A verb is an action word.
动词是做事情的词，比如跑、跳、吃。
Do you remember when we played Simon Says
你们还记得几周前我们玩“老师说”
a couple of weeks ago?
游戏吗？
Yes?
记得吗？
What are some of the words that you
你们从“老师说”游戏中学到
learned from Simon Says?
了哪些词呢？
Here are some that I remember.
这些是我记得的一些。
Play, walk, run, eat, jump, stomp, clap,
Play, walk, run, eat, jump, stomp, clap,
drink, read, write, sit, close, open.
drink, read, write, sit, close, open.
Do you know any others?
你们还知道其他的吗？
Do you remember more?
还记得更多吗？
Let's practice together some more.
让我们再一起练习一些。
I will test you on your pronunciation later.
我稍后会听听你们怎么发音。
For this activity, you're going to need a
这个活动，你们需要一支铅笔
pencil and a piece of paper.
和一张纸。
Watch the images and write the word for
观看图片，然后写下你们看到的
the images that you see.
图片对应的单词。
When you understand the images, you will be
当你们理解了这些图片，你们就能够
able to play a communication game with your
和你们的同学一起玩一个交流游戏。
classmates.
同学们。
Let's do this activity together first.
我们先一起来做这个活动。
Okay, number one is clap, clap,
好的，第一个是 clap, clap (拍手 pāishǒu),
like that.
像这样。
Number two, number two is close,
第二个，第二个是 close (关上 guānshang),
close, like that.
close, 像这样。
Number three, number three is drink, drink,
第三个，第三个是 drink (喝 hē), drink,
drink, drink.
drink, drink.
Number four is eat,
第四个是 eat (吃 chī),
eat, eat, eat.
eat, eat, eat.
Number five is jump, j-u-m-p.
第五个是 jump (跳 tiào), j-u-m-p.
J-u-m-p, j-u-m-p.
J-u-m-p, j-u-m-p.
Number six is open, o-p, open,
第六个是 open (打开 dǎkāi), o-p, open,
open.
open.
Number seven, play, p-l-a-y.
第七个，play (玩 wán / 演奏 yǎnzòu), p-l-a-y.
Number eight, number eight is read, r-e
第八个，第八个是 read (读 dú), r-e
-a-d, read.
-a-d, read.
Number nine, number nine is run, n
第九个，第九个是 run (跑 pǎo), n
-r-u-n.
-r-u-n.
Number 10 is sit, s-i
第十个是 sit (坐 zuò), s-i
-t, not e, not seat, s-i-t,
-t, 不是 e, 不是 seat, s-i-t,
sit.
sit.
Number 11, 11 is stomp, s-t,
第十一个，十一个是 stomp (跺脚 duòjiǎo), s-t,
stomp.
stomp.
Number 12 is walk, walk.
第十二个是 walk (走 zǒu), walk.
This letter is silent, walk.
这个字母不发音，walk.
Last one, number 13, 13, write, write.
最后一个，第十三个，十三个，write (写 xiě), write.
This letter is silent, write.
这个字母不发音，write.